Hi.
In this segment we're going to talk about consecutive rolls.
And what that means is doing a roll, and a roll, and a roll, and a roll, without stopping, without breaking any of the, any of the motion.
And the trick of that is, is right when the Frisbee comes to your second hand, is to push it up, right in the right angle, so it comes back to your other hand.
And it's again, it's the using your legs and using your arms.
But the last part is the critical part, to have it come here, so it sets up for your next roll.
An example of consecutive rolls: here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here, here.
Now if you noticed, every time that it came around to this arm, I was pushing it up, so it was almost right in the right spot for my next roll.
I didn't have to run around.
So the whole key is, is that right at the end and that push to make sure that it's set for the next roll.